"Hey baby, wanna go look for houses
in neighborhoods with good schools"?
Again, I'm sorry. With Howard
and Bernadette getting married...
...l got caught up
in a little wedding fever.
l take it back.
(Penny:)You can't take something like that back.
What are we supposed to do now?
(Leonard:)Okay, at some point, we'll look back
and this is going to be a funny story.
(Leonard:)Why don't we just start
doing that now?
- You're kidding.
- No.
(Leonard:)Hey, do you remember...
(Leonard:)...that time when I proposed to you
in bed, heh?
(Leonard:)And you were all, like,
"What are you doing"?
(Leonard:)That was so funny.
(Leonard:)So funny.
- It's not funny.
- Just give it a minute.
ls that a little smile I see there?